{
    "subject": "resource/Handicapped_Future",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:German_short_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Handicapped Future is German short films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6831742525100708,
            "question": "What is the subject of 'Handicapped Future'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6550569534301758,
            "question": "Is 'Handicapped Future' focused on a specific genre of film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6318033933639526,
            "question": "Where are the films in 'Handicapped Future' from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5882174372673035,
            "question": "What type of films are featured in 'Handicapped Future'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4996550679206848,
            "question": "How are disability and the future portrayed in 'Handicapped Future'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4942787289619446,
            "question": "Are there any common elements or styles found in the films of 'Handicapped Future'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4698851704597473,
            "question": "Where can one find more information about 'Handicapped Future'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45612800121307373,
            "question": "What impact might 'Handicapped Future' have on viewers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.415914922952652,
            "question": "Are there any similar film collections or movements to 'Handicapped Future'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3488064408302307,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the themes explored in 'Handicapped Future'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Handicapped Future is German short films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5277_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any similar film collections or movements to 'Handicapped Future'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5277_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact might 'Handicapped Future' have on viewers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5277_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can one find more information about 'Handicapped Future'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5277_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5277_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5277_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5277_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5277_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5277_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5277_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5277_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5277_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5277_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5277_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n\n\nThe documents all state that \"Handicapped Future\" is a documentary about disabled children in West Germany, not short films. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`\n\nThe documents describe \"Handicapped Future\" as a documentary about disabled children in West Germany, their treatment by society, and the importance of disability access. The subject of \"Handicapped Future\" is not German short films, but rather a documentary film about a specific social issue in West Germany."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents discuss the documentary film \"Handicapped Future\" by Werner Herzog, focusing on its content which revolves around disabled children in West Germany. There is no information provided about the subject being German short films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Handicapped Future is a German documentary film, not a short film.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several passages discuss the film focusing on disabled children in West Germany, their treatment, and societal perceptions within Germany.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Handicapped Future is actually a documentary film about the treatment of physically handicapped children in West Germany, not German short films.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The subject of Handicapped Future is disabled children in West Germany, not German short films.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}